ظآزThe whole world is lit upظآز
ظآزBecause you existظآز
ظآزYou're alwaysظآز
ظآزSomewhere close, flying with meظآز
ظآزGo to where the wind blowsظآز
ظآزHold tightظآز
ظآزTo the ray of light that belongs to usظآز
=Wild & Fiery=
=Episode 22=
Mr. He, what brings you here today?
I heard that you
are very capable, Miss Yan,
so I wanted to meet you.
Is Mr. Hong
not here today?
I'm sorry, Mr. He.
Mr. Hong has been away lately,
and he doesn't see people easily.
Then, it's really
unfortunate today.
What a pity.
I originally had a collaboration
I wanted to discuss with Mr. Hong.
What collaboration?
Why don't you tell me about it?
You are a smart person,
so I'll be blunt.
He Group
wants to cooperate with Mr. Hong
to auction his new work,
"Changing Mountains and Rivers."
Why are you here?
Boss,
your rival is causing trouble again.
What is he up to now?
He's looking for Hong
to deal with you.
Why are you here?
Miss Mu,
don't get the wrong idea.
I'm here for business.
Don't be so nervous.
I was just curious
and dropped by to take a look.
If you want to talk business later,
you can just go to the office.
I came here today
to give you an important piece of news.
I don't want others to know.
What news?
He Min
wants to secure Mr. Hong's new work,
"Changing Mountains and Rivers."
He plans to use it
to outshine the Mu Group at the auction.
The message is delivered.
I'm leaving now.
Don't worry.
He Min won't succeed.
But last time, our Mu Group
completely offended Mr. Hong.
I'm afraid he really will choose He Min.
Miss Yan has already come to warn us.
Maybe there's still a chance.
Try this.
To our first official date,
cheers.
Since it's our first date,
you should be more focused.
You guessed what I was thinking again?
Then, guess what I'm thinking?
Could it be
that you have other arrangements?
Now, leave yourself to me.
I'll be your eyes.
Is this another way
for you to decompress?
Wait and see.
You're very different today.
Where did you learn this?
ظآزBefore boarding the planeظآز
We're here.
ظآزYou are about to leave meظآز
ظآزFar behindظآز
ظآزThe luggage in handظآز
ظآزIs both strange and familiarظآز
ظآزWe once made a promiseظآز
ظآزTo leave our footprints
all over the worldظآز
ظآزBut unfortunately, nowظآز
ظآزYou broke that promiseظآز
ظآزThe world you want to chaseظآز
You prepared all this for me?
Do you like it?
I designed these for you myself.
ظآزWatching you goظآز
So,
this is what
you've been drawing all this time?
ظآزAn innocent promiseظآز
ظآزI thought everything
would go as plannedظآز
ظآزBut unfortunately, nowظآز
ظآزWe've gone our separate waysظآز
You know how to draw?
ظآزWatching you walk away quietlyظآز
What other surprises
are you hiding from me?
It's just some doodling.
It's nothing special.
Grandpa and Mom
were both great artists.
You must have
a natural talent for it too.
If you ever create
a piece you're satisfied with,
remember to tell me.
ظآزOnly I am left in the crowdظآز
ظآزWalking aloneظآز
Well?
Does it look good?
It looks good.
My wife looks good in anything.
Captain Shen, don't call me that.
I'm still an unmarried woman.
Who's your wife?
ظآزYour freedomظآز
After the auction ends,
let's get married.
ظآزMy hand brushed across the smile
on the photoظآز
ظآزA cup of wine full of sorrowظآز
ظآزLooking up,
there's the beautiful starry skyظآز
ظآزYou told meظآز
ظآزIt would shine like the starsظآز
ظآزBut you forgot to tell meظآز
ظآزHow do I live after losing you?ظآز
ظآزWhen I look up at the distant starsظآز
ظآزEverything is hazyظآز
ظآزLight comes beaming inظآز
ظآزLanding on my skinظآز
ظآزWarms the space you left behindظآز
ظآزShadows move aroundظآز
ظآزAwake, racing thoughtsظآز
ظآزTry to keep the memories safeظآز
ظآزDon't slip awayظآز
ظآزI'm all yours, all yoursظآز